<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<component type="desktop-application">
  <id>org.kde.lskat.desktop</id>
  <metadata_license>FSFAP</metadata_license>
  <project_license>GPL-2.0+</project_license>
  <name>LSkat</name>
  <name xml:lang="ca">LSkat</name>
  <name xml:lang="ca-valencia">LSkat</name>
  <name xml:lang="cs">LSkat</name>
  <name xml:lang="da">LSkat</name>
  <name xml:lang="de">Offiziersskat</name>
  <name xml:lang="el">LSkat</name>
  <name xml:lang="en-GB">LSkat</name>
  <name xml:lang="es">LSkat</name>
  <name xml:lang="et">LSkat</name>
  <name xml:lang="eu">LSkat</name>
  <name xml:lang="fi">LSkat</name>
  <name xml:lang="fr">LSkat</name>
  <name xml:lang="gl">LSkat</name>
  <name xml:lang="id">LSkat</name>
  <name xml:lang="it">LSkat</name>
  <name xml:lang="ko">LSkat</name>
  <name xml:lang="nl">LSkat</name>
  <name xml:lang="nn">LSkat</name>
  <name xml:lang="pl">LSkat</name>
  <name xml:lang="pt">LSkat</name>
  <name xml:lang="pt-BR">LSkat</name>
  <name xml:lang="sk">LSkat</name>
  <name xml:lang="sl">LSkat</name>
  <name xml:lang="sr">П‑скат</name>
  <name xml:lang="sr-Latn">P‑skat</name>
  <name xml:lang="sr-ijekavian">П‑скат</name>
  <name xml:lang="sr-ijekavianlatin">P‑skat</name>
  <name xml:lang="sv">Officersskat</name>
  <name xml:lang="uk">LSkat</name>
  <name xml:lang="x-test">xxLSkatxx</name>
  <name xml:lang="zh-CN">LSkat</name>
  <name xml:lang="zh-TW">LSkat</name>
  <summary>German card game Skat for two players</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ca">Joc de cartes alemany Skat per a dos jugadors</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ca-valencia">Joc de cartes alemany Skat per a dos jugadors</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="cs">Německá karetní hra Skat pro dva hráče</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="da">Det tyske kortspil Skat for to spillere</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="de">Deutsches Kartenspiel Skat für zwei Spieler</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="el">Γερμανικό παιχνίδι καρτών Skat για δύο παίκτες</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="en-GB">German card game Skat for two players</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="es">Juego de cartas alemán Skat para dos jugadores</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="et">Saksa kaardimäng skatt kahele mängijale</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="eu">Bi jokalarirentzako Skat karta joko alemana</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="fi">Saksalainen skat-korttipeli kahdelle pelaajalle</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="fr">Jeu de cartes allemand « Skat » pour deux joueurs</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="id">Permainan kartu Skat Jerman untuk dua pemain</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="it">Gioco di carte tedesco Skat per due giocatori</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ko">2인용 독일식 카드 게임 스카트</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="nl">Duits kaartspel Skat voor twee spelers</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="nn">Det tyske kortspelet Skat for to spelarar</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="pl">Niemiecka gra karciana Skat dla dwóch graczy</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="pt">O jogo de cartão alemão Skat para dois jogadores</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="pt-BR">Jogo de cartas alemão Tenente Skat para dois jogadores</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="sl">Nemška igra Skat za dva igralca</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="sv">Tyskt kortspel Skat för två spelare</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="uk">Німецька карткова гра «Скат» для двох гравців</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="x-test">xxGerman card game Skat for two playersxx</summary>
  <description>
    <p>
      Lieutenant Skat (from German "Offiziersskat") is a fun and engaging card game for two players,
      where the second player is either live opponent, or a built in artificial intelligence.
    </p>
    <p xml:lang="ca">El Tinent Skat (de l'alemany «Offiziersskat», en anglès «Lieutenant Skat») és un joc de cartes divertit i captivador per a dos jugadors, on el segon jugador és un contrari real, o un construït amb intel·ligència artificial.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ca-valencia">El Tinent Skat (de l'alemany «Offiziersskat», en anglés «Lieutenant Skat») és un joc de cartes divertit i captivador per a dos jugadors, on el segon jugador és un contrari real, o un construït amb intel·ligència artificial.</p>
    <p xml:lang="cs">Poručík Skat (z německého "Offiziersskat") je zábavná a podmanivá hra pro dva hráče, kde druhý hráč je buď skutečný protihráč, nebo umělá inteligence.</p>
    <p xml:lang="da">Løjtnant Skat (fra det tyske "Offiziersskat") er et sjovt og medrivende kortspil for to spilere, hvor den anden spiller enten er et menneske eller indbygget kunstig intelligens..</p>
    <p xml:lang="de">Offiziersskat ist ein Kartenspiel für zwei Spieler, bei dem der zweite Spieler entweder ein menschlicher Gegner sein kann, oder durch die eingebaute KI gestellt wird.</p>
    <p xml:lang="el">Ο υπολοχαγός Skat (από τα Γερμανικά «Offiziersskat») είναι ένα διασκεδαστικό και συναρπαστικό παιχνίδι καρτών για δύο παίκτες, με τον δεύτερο παίκτη να είναι ένας ζωντανός αντίπαλος ή μια ενσωματωμένη τεχνητή νοημοσύνη.</p>
    <p xml:lang="en-GB">Lieutenant Skat (from German "Offiziersskat") is a fun and engaging card game for two players, where the second player is either live opponent, or a built in artificial intelligence.</p>
    <p xml:lang="es">El Teniente Skat (en alemán, «Offiziersskat») es un juego de cartas divertido y cautivador para dos jugadores, en el que el otro jugador puede ser un amigo o la computadora.</p>
    <p xml:lang="et">Leitnant Skat (saksa keeles Offiziersskat) on lõbus ja köitev kahe mängijaga mäng, kus vastaseks võib olla nii inimene kui ka arvuti.</p>
    <p xml:lang="eu">Skat Tenientea (Lotinant Skat, alemaneko «Offiziersskat») bi jokalarirentzako karta-joko dibertigarri eta erakargarria da, eta bigarren jokalaria aurkari biziduna da, edo adimen artifizialean eraikia.</p>
    <p xml:lang="fi">Luutnantti-skat (saksan Offiziersskat) on hauska ja viihdyttävä kahden pelaajan korttipeli, missä toinen pelaajista on joko ihminen tai tekoäly.</p>
    <p xml:lang="fr">Le Skat (de l'allemand « Offiziersskat ») est un jeu de cartes amusant et ludique pour deux joueurs, le second joueur peut être un humain ou une intelligence artificielle.</p>
    <p xml:lang="gl">O Tenente Skat (do alemán «Offizierskat») é un xogo de cartas para dous xogadores no que o segundo xogador tanto pode ser un adversario ao vivo ou un xogador de intelixencia artificial.</p>
    <p xml:lang="id">Lieutenant Skat (dari German "Offiziersskat") adalah sebuah permainan yang menyenangkan dan permainan kartu yang menarik untuk dua pemain, dimana pemain kedua adalah antara lawan hidup, atau dibangun dalam kecerdasan buatan.</p>
    <p xml:lang="it">Tenente Skat (dal tedesco «Offiziersskat») è un gioco di carte divertente e coinvolgente per due giocatori, in cui il secondo giocatore è una persona o un'intelligenza artificiale.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ko">스카트 중사(독일어 "Offiziersskat"에서 따 옴)는 2인용 카드 게임입니다. 두 번째 플레이어는 사람이나 AI 둘 다가 될 수 있습니다.</p>
    <p xml:lang="nl">Luitenant Skat (uit het Duits  "Offiziersskat) is een leuk en uitdagend kaartspel voor twee spelers, waar de tweede speler ofwel een levende tegenstander is of ingebouwd met kunstmatige intelligentie.</p>
    <p xml:lang="nn">Løytnant Skat (frå tysk: «Offiziersskat») er eit morosamt kortspel for to spelarar. Du kan anten spela mot ein annan spelar eller mot datamaskina.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pl">Porucznik Skat (z niemieckiego "Offiziersskat") jest wciągającą grą karcianą dla dwóch graczy, w której drugi gracz jest żywy lub sztuczną inteligencją.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pt">O Tenente Skat (do Alemão "Offiziersskat") é um jogo de cartas engraçado e viciante para dois jogadores, onde o segundo jogador é um adversário ao vivo ou um baseado em inteligência artificial.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pt-BR">Tenente Skat (do alemão "Offiziersskat") é um jogo de cartas para dois jogadores onde o segundo jogador ou é um adversário real ou uma construção feita com inteligência artificial.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sk">Poručík Skar (z nemčiny "Offiziersskat") je zábavná a podmanivá kartová hra pre dvoch hráčov, kde druhý hráč je živý protivník alebo vstavaná umelá inteligencia. </p>
    <p xml:lang="sl">Lieutenant Skat (iz nemškega imena »Offiziersskat«) je zabavna igra s kartami za dva igralca, v kateri je drugi igralec bodisi človeški bodisi vgrajeni računalniški igralec z umetno inteligenco.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sr">Поручник Скат (од немачког „Offiziersskat“) представља забавну и заразну игру са картама за два играча, где је други играч или живи противник или уграђена вештачка интелигенција.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sr-Latn">Poručnik Skat (od nemačkog „Offiziersskat“) predstavlja zabavnu i zaraznu igru sa kartama za dva igrača, gde je drugi igrač ili živi protivnik ili ugrađena veštačka inteligencija.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sr-ijekavian">Поручник Скат (од немачког „Offiziersskat“) представља забавну и заразну игру са картама за два играча, где је други играч или живи противник или уграђена вештачка интелигенција.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sr-ijekavianlatin">Poručnik Skat (od nemačkog „Offiziersskat“) predstavlja zabavnu i zaraznu igru sa kartama za dva igrača, gde je drugi igrač ili živi protivnik ili ugrađena veštačka inteligencija.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sv">Officersskat (från tyskans "Offiziersskat") är ett roligt och engagerande kortspel för två spelare, där den andra spelaren antingen är en verklig motspelare, eller den inbyggda artificiella intelligensen.</p>
    <p xml:lang="tr">Teğmen Skat (Almacada, "Offiziersskat"), iki oyunculu, eğlenceli ve ilgi çekici bir kart oyunudur, buradaki ikinci oyuncu, canlı bir rakip veya yapay zekadır.</p>
    <p xml:lang="uk">Лейтенант Скат (німецькою «Offiziersskat») — це весела і захоплива гра у карти для двох гравців, у якій вашим суперником може бути або людина, або вбудований штучний комп’ютерний інтелект</p>
    <p xml:lang="x-test">xxLieutenant Skat (from German "Offiziersskat") is a fun and engaging card game for two players, where the second player is either live opponent, or a built in artificial intelligence.xx</p>
  </description>
  <url type="bugtracker">https://bugs.kde.org/enter_bug.cgi?format=guided&amp;product=lskat</url>
  <url type="help">https://docs.kde.org/?application=lskat</url>
  <url type="donation">https://www.kde.org/community/donations/?app=lskat&amp;source=appdata</url>
  <screenshots>
    <screenshot type="default">
      <image>https://cdn.kde.org/screenshots/lskat/lskat.png</image>
    </screenshot>
  </screenshots>
  <project_group>KDE</project_group>
  <provides>
    <binary>lskat</binary>
  </provides>
  <releases>
    <release version="1.50.20123" date="2021-03-04"/>
    <release version="1.50.20122" date="2021-02-04"/>
    <release version="1.50.20121" date="2021-01-07"/>
    <release version="1.50.20120" date="2020-12-10"/>
  </releases>
</component>
